Guide to the Calvin Bryce Hoover Papers, 1922-1970
Duke University. University Archives
- Academic Material
  - Joerg, Frederick C., 1947-1958 (Box 43)
  - Kreps, Juanita, 1947, undated (Box 43)
  - Landon, Charles E., 1945-1957 (Box 43)
  - Lemert, Benjamin Franklin, 1945-1955 (Box 43)
  - McKenzie, Lionel W., 1948-1956 (Box 43)
  - Ratchford, Benjamin U., 1943-1956 (Box 43)
  - Saville, Lloyd, 1952-1959 (Box 43)
  - Schwenning, G. T., 1947-1948 (Box 43)
  - Shields, John Herman, 1945, 1948-1949 (Box 43)
  - Simmons, Edward C., 1947-1958 (Box 43)
  - Smith, Robert S., 1941-1959 (Box 43)
  - Spengler, Joseph J., 1932-1949 (Box 43)
  - Spengler, Joseph J., 1950-1957, 1966 (Box 44)
  - Tower, Ralph B. (Econ 12) (Box 44)
  - Class Census (Box 44)
  - Commonwealth Seminar, 1962 (Box 44)
  - Dissertations under Hoover (list) (Box 44)
  - Course Outlines and Reading Lists, Econ 193-316 (Box 44)
  - Doctoral Examinations, 1965-1966 (Box 44)
  - Economics Dept. Requirements and Reading List (Box 44)
  - Econ 313 Team Questions (Box 44)
  - Economic Systems (Class notes, exams, etc.) (Box 44)
  - Economic Systems (Class notes), 1946 (Box 44)
  - Economic Theory, miscellaneous (Box 44)
  - Economic Theory, profit (Box 44)
  - Exams (Box 45)
  - Lecture Notes (Box 45)
  - General and Student-Prepared Bibliographies (Box 45)
  - Lecture Notes and Syllabi (Box 45)
  - Lecture Notes, Russia (Box 45)
  - Lecture Notes, the Firm (Box 45)
  - Paper and Report Topics (Box 45)
  - Prelim Exams (Box 45)
  - Examination Questions, 1964, 1966 (Box 45)
  - Reserve Reading Lists (Econ 194, 215, 216, 293, 294) (Box 45)
  - Reserve Reading Lists (Econ 313, 314) (Box 45)
  - Reserve Reading Lists (Econ 315, 316) (Box 45)
  - Theory Class Material (Econ 313, 314) (Box 46)
  - Theory Notes (Box 46)
  - Econmics Dept., Honors and Requirements for Advanced Degrees, 1950, 1955 (Box 46)
  - Department Matters, 1961-1967 (Box 46)
  - Budgetary Materials, 1955-1956 (Box 46)
  - Economics Dept., 1938-1948 (Box 46)
  - Economics Dept., 1949-1950 (Box 46)
  - Economics Dept., 1951-1953 (Box 46)
  - Class Material from the Univ. of Minnesota (Box 47)
  - Curriculum Vitae (Box 47)
  - Economic and Business Administration, 1949-1953 (Box 47)
  - Economics (miscellaneous) (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Economic Trends Lecture: Europe 1952 (Box 47)
  - Economic Undergraduate Faculty (Box 47)
  - General Economics, Univ. of Minnesota, 1923 (Box 47)
  - Presidential Committee, 1960 (Box 48 RESTRICTED)
  - Presidential Committee, through 1960 Nov. 28 (Box 48 RESTRICTED)
  - Presidential Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 48 RESTRICTED)
  - Presidential Committee, Letters, 1960-1961 (Box 48 RESTRICTED)
  - Introduction to Economic History, Univ. of Minnesota (Box 49)
  - Reduction in Teaching Load Applications (Box 49)
  - Research Applications (Box 49)
  - Research Publications (Box 49)
  - Univ. of Minnesota, circa 1923-1924 (Box 49)
  - Economics Dept., 1954-1960, 1966 (Box 49)
  - Summary of Student Poll of Professors (Box 49)
- Professional Associations
  - American Economic Association (AEA)
    - Programs, 1952-1953 (Box 49)
    - Galley Proof, Presidential Address, 1953-1954 (Box 49)
    - Business Meeting, 1952 (Box 49)
    - Bell, James W., 1953-1954 (Box 49)
    - Agenda Correspondence, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Correspondence on Arrangements and Congratulations, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Memo from Hoover to Participants, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Burgess, Randolph, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Mid-Century Conference, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1953-1954 (Box 49)
    - Session I, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Session X, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Session XI, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session II, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Schultz, T., 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session IX, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session V, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session III, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session IV, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session VI, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session VII, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session XIII, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Clemens, E. W., 1953 (Box 50)
    - Bowen's Report, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session XV, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session XII, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session XIV, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Session XVI, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Growth Session, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Harris, S., 1953 (Box 50)
    - Williams, John H., 1953 (Box 50)
    - Lewis, Ben, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Economic Implications of an Aging Population Session, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Friendly, Alfred, Publicity, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Local Arrangements Committee, 1953 (Box 50)
    - Research and Publications Committee, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Snavely, Tipton, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Ad Hoc Committee, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Honors and Awards Committee, 1953 (Box 51)
    - American Statistical Association, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Main Papers, Letter, 1953 (Box 51)
    - International Economic Association, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Ford Foundation, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Harberler, Gottfried, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Initial Correspondence on Arranging AEA Meeting, 1953 (Box 51)
    - Material on 1948 Meeting (Box 51)
    - Honors and Awards Committee, 1949 Meeting (Box 51)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1935-1949 (Box 51)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 51)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 51)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1960-1964 (Box 52)
    - General/Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 52)
    - Distinguished Fellow Award, 1965 (Box 52)
  - Southern Economic Association (SEA)
    - A, 1952-1953 (Box 52)
    - Agricultural Economics Roundtable, 1952 (Box 52)
    - B, 1952-1954 (Box 52)
    - C, 1952 (Box 52)
    - D, 1952 (Box 52)
    - Daane's Paper and Discussants, 1952 (Box 52)
    - Executive Committee, 1952 (Box 53)
    - F, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Friday Afternoon Session, 1952 (Box 53)
    - G, 1953-1954 (Box 53)
    - H, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Holly, Prof. J. Fred, 1952-1955 (Box 53)
    - I, 1953 (Box 53)
    - L, 1952-1954 (Box 53)
    - Leland, Dean Simeon, 1952 (Box 53)
    - Mc, 1952 (Box 53)
    - McCracken, Harlan L., 1952 (Box 53)
    - McFerrin,John B., 1951-1955 (Box 53)
    - M, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Marketing Roundtable, 1952 (Box 53)
    - R, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Rediscovering Interest Rates, 1952 (Box 53)
    - S, 1953 (Box 53)
    - Schwenning, G. T., 1948-1955 (Box 53)
    - Siefkin, Gordon, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Smith, Howard R., 1951-1955 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association Expenses, 1952-1953 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1936-1951 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1951-1964 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1946 Meeting (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1965-1966 (Box 53)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1967 (Box 53)
    - Stocking, Dr. George W., 1951-1953 (Box 54)
    - T, 1953 (Box 54)
    - V, 1953 (Box 54)
    - W, 1952-1953 (Box 54)
    - Woosley, John B., 1950-1952 (Box 54)
  - Ford Foundation
    - Summer Seminar, 1961 (Box 54)
    - Applications for Summer Seminar, 1961 (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - Ford Economic Systems Summer Seminar (Box 54)
    - Reading List, Ford Summer Seminar, 1961 (Box 54)
    - Letter to Tom Carroll for Mr. Lanning, 1959 (Box 54)
    - Faculty Research Fellowship, 1960-1962 (Box 54)
    - Research Funds, Requests and Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 54)
    - General (i.e, correspondence, memoranda, etc.), 1956-1959 (Box 54)
    - Applications for Grant Money, 1957 (Box 55)
    - Reports on Grants Given in 1957 (Box 55)
    - Applications for Grant Money, 1958 (Box 55)
    - Reports on Grants Given in 1958 (Box 55)
    - Applications for Grant Money, 1959 (Box 55)
    - Reports on Grants Given in 1959 (Box 55)
    - Grants Awarded for Summer, 1959 (Box 55)
    - Applications for Grant Money, 1960 (Box 55)
    - Reports on Grants Given in 1960 (Box 55)
    - Applications for Grant Money, 1962 (Box 55)
- Government Service
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Drought Relief Service, 1934 November 3 (Box 55)
  - The Drought of 1934, A Report of the Federal Government's Assistance to Agriculture as of July 15, 1935 (Box 56)
  - Congressional Testimony, 1944-1945 (Box 56)
  - National War College Executive Board, 1949 (Box 56)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1943 (Box 56)
  - Correspondence, Committee for Economic Development, A-H, 1944-1948 (Box 56)
  - Correspondence, Committee for Economic Development, I-V, 1943-1949 (Box 56)
  - Correspondence (regarding service in war agencies, 1940-1942 and in preparation for mission to Germany, 1945) 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1943-1948 (Box 57)
  - American Committee for International Studies, 1941 (Box 57)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration China, circa 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - Honerkamp, Rose, 1948 (Box 57)
  - European Recovery Program Memoranda, circa 1948 (Box 57)
  - European Recovery Program Printed Material, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, B, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, C, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, D, 1947 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, F, 1947 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, G, 1947-1949 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, K-L, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, M, 1947 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, P-S, 1947-1948 (Box 57)
  - President's Committee on Foreign Aid, Correspondence, T-Y, 1947 (Box 57)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA) Press Releases, 1948 (Box 57)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration (ECA), 1947-1949 (Box 57)
  - Economic Intelligence Reports, 1945 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 57)
  - Economic Intelligence Reports, 1945 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 58)
  - Economic Intelligence Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 58)
  - Army of Occupation, 1945-1946 (Box 58)
  - Board of Economic Warfare, 1941-1942 (Box 58)
  - Board of Economic Warfare Organizational Chart, 1942 (Box 58)
  - European Movement, 1949 (Box 58)
  - European Movement, London Trip, 1949 (Box 58)
  - German Reconstruction, 1945-1946 (Box 58)
  - National Defense Material, 1941-1942 (Box 59)
  - Special Consultant, Dept. of the Army, 1947-1948 (Box 59)
  - Government Travel Data, 1947 (Box 59)
  - War Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 59)
  - Smith, Lt. Gen. W. B., 1950-1956 (Box 59)
  - Office of Strategic Services, 1943-1945, 1952 (Box 59)
  - National Defense Executive Reserve, 1957-1958 (Box 59)
  - Tikander, Wilho (includes information about the Office of Strategic Services), 1959 (Box 59)
  - A Minimum German Standard of Living in Relation to Industrial Disarmament and Reparatons, report by Hoover to German Standard of Living Board, 1945 Sept. 10 (Box 59)
  - The Future Level of German Industry, report to the members of the Economic Directorate, 1946 Jan. 28 (Box 59)
  - War Time Report on the U. S., Germany and Russia, 1940-1942 (Box 60)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (Box 60)
  - O.E.E.C. Report No. 2, circa 1950 (Box 60)
  - Security Clearance Forms (Box 60)
  - Economic Growth (Joint Committee) (Box 60)
  - Codex, 1950-1956 (Box 60)
  - German Occupation, 1946-1947 (in Box 75, legal size folder) (Box 60)
- Subject Files
  - Accident Report (Injury) (Box 60)
  - Agricultural Policy Institute, 1966-1967 (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - Air War College, 1963 (Box 60)
  - Allied Social Sciences Associations, 1964 (Box 60)
  - Altvater, F. V. (Box 61)
  - Articles, 1930s, late 1950s-1971 (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Association for the Study of Soviet-Type Economies, 1962-1963 (Box 61)
  - Belgrade, 1958 (Box 61)
  - Berlin, 1958 (Box 61)
  - Bibliography, Intelligence (Box 61)
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1961 (Box 61)
  - Carnegie Corp., Annual Report, 1965 (Box 61)
  - Chapel Hill Speech, 1959 Dec. 11 (Box 61)
  - China, 1959 (Box 61)
  - Codes, Duke University (Box 62)
  - Commencement Addresses (Data for) (Box 62)
  - Demosthenes and Cicero (Box 62)
  - Duke Endowment (Box 62)
  - Duke University Press, 1952-1965 (Box 62)
  - DuPont Report, 1958 (Box 62)
  - Eckstein Report, 1960 (Box 62)
  - Economic Development Research (Box 62)
  - Economics Professors' Publications in Response to Hoover's Letter of 1947 Nov. 14 (Box 62)
  - Economic Statistics in Leading Universities (Box 62)
  - Edens Inauguration, 1949 (Box 62)
  - Esso Discussion Group, 1960-1964 (Box 62)
  - European Trip, 1950 (Box 62)
  - European Reactions to Korean Crisis (Box 62)
  - Faculty Club, circa 1927-1928, 1950, 1964 (Box 62)
  - Faculty Council, circa early 1960s, 1965 (Box 62)
  - Faculty Fringe Benefits (Box 62)
  - Faculty Reorganization, 1950s (Box 62)
  - Fellowships (Duke Univ.), 1952-1953 (Box 62)
  - Fellowships (Other Schools), 1948-1949 (Box 62)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 62)
  - Foreign Exchange Education, 1947 (Box 62)
  - Frey, Otto (Box 62)
  - Fulbright, 1955-1960 (Box 62)
  - Germany (Box 62)
  - Graduate Degree Requirement in Economics (Box 63)
  - Graduates Newsletter, 1964 (Box 63)
  - Graduate Students in Economics, Fall 1966 (Box 63)
  - Grossman, Gregory (Box 63)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1958-1960 (Box 63)
  - Harris, Norman Wait (Box 63)
  - Harvard Business Review (Box 63)
  - High School Text (Joint Council on Economic Education), Rough Copies and Incomplete Ones (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - High School Text (Joint Council on Economic Education), Complete Copies (Box 63)
  - Hiss, Alger (Box 63)
  - How to Make and Industrial Survey (Box 63)
  - Interviews, Germany (Box 63)
  - Itineraries (Box 63)
  - Khruschev's Speech in the Supreme Soviet, 1960 May 5 (Box 63)
  - Knight, B. W. (poem) (Box 63)
  - Kyklos Project, circa 1958 (Box 64)
  - Lange, Oscar, circa 1943 (Box 64)
  - LeFigaro, 1950 (Box 64)
  - Lester, R. A. (reprints), 1945-1946 (Box 64)
  - Letters to be Carried, Hotels (trips) (Box 64)
  - Library (Box 64)
  - Life Officers Investment Seminar, 1960 June 17-18, Chicago (Box 64)
  - The Little Golden Calf (Box 64)
  - [Duke University] Long-Range Planning Reports, 1959, 1960 (Box 64)
  - Maps (Box 64)
  - Medal of Freedom, 1946-1947 (Box 64)
  - Meeting on Candidates for Lectureship at Univ. of Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1955 Nov. 30, Washington, D. C. (Box 64)
  - Meetings, Agendas, Etc., 1947-1949 (Box 64)
  - Merrill Center, 1955-1956 (Box 64)
  - Merrill Center Conference, 1961 (Box 65)
  - Mortality Trends in the U. S., 1900-1949, American Medical Association, 1952 (Box 65)
  - Moscow, 1958 (Box 65)
  - National War College Seminar, 1960 (Box 65)
  - New Deal, 1934, 1940 (Box 65)
  - North Carolina, Univ. of (Information on consolidation) (Box 65)
  - Notes on Labor Problems (Box 65)
  - Paris, 1945 (Box 65)
  - Personnel Manuals, 1960s (Box 65)
  - Perspectives Article, 1954 (Box 65)
  - Poland, 1959 (Box 65)
  - Prague, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Publicity, 1930s-1950s (Box 65)
  - Publicity, Clippings (4 folders) (Box 65)
  - Publicity, Clippings (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Publishers, Directory (Box 66)
  - Quotations (Box 66)
  - Railroads, 1961-1963 (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Ratliff, C. E., 1959 (Box 67)
  - Research Topics (Box 67)
  - Ropp, Theodore (Box 67)
  - Russia (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - Russian Fellowship Aid, 1959 (Box 67)
  - Russian Material, 1959 (Box 67)
  - Russian Area Division (Box 67)
  - Russian Studies at Duke University, 1944-1947 (Box 67)
  - Russian Revolutionary Bibliography (Box 67)
  - Russian Living Standards (Box 67)
  - Russia, Clippings (5 folders) (Box 67)
  - Russia Trip, 1929-1930 (includes passport) (Box 68)
  - Russia Trip Correspondence, 1956 (Box 68)
  - Russia Trip Clippings, 1956 (Box 68)
  - Russia Trip, 1956 (Box 68)
  - Russia Trip, 1958 (Box 68)
  - Schiro, Victor (Box 68)
  - Schultz, Theodore W. (Box 68)
  - Screwball File (Box 68)
  - Shares of Upper Income Groups in Income and Savings, Kuznets (Box 68)
  - Shipkov, Michael (Box 68)
  - Southern Bell Telephone Company Conference, 1964 (Box 68)
  - Southern Bell Telephone Company Seminar, 1962-1964 (Box 68)
  - Southern Conference on Slavic Studies (Box 68)
  - Soviet-Chinese Conflicts (Seminar), 1964 (Box 69)
  - Soviet Economics, 1958 (Box 69)
  - Soviet Students (Box 69)
  - Soviet Union Retail Prices, 1936-1939 (Box 69)
  - Student's Guide to Duke Faculty, 1964 (Box 69)
  - Testimony regarding AT&T, 1966 (Box 69)
  - Theoretical Problems of Socialism (Box 69)
  - University Council on Research, 1959-1960 (Box 69)
  - Warsaw, 1958 (Box 69)
  - Washington, DC, 1958 (Box 69)
  - Who's Who (Box 69)
  - Williams, B. Frederick, Jr., Thesis (Box 69)
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation (Box 69)
  - Workman's Comp Act (Box 69)
- Audio-Visual Material
  - Hoover Reception and Dinner Tapes, 1966 May 9 (Box 69)
  - Photographs, Academic (Box 70)
  - Photographs, Family (Box 70)
  - Photographs, Government (Box 70)
  - Photographs, Portraits (Box 70)
  - Photographs, Russia Trip, 1956 (Box 70)
- Personal
  - Date Books from [1939], 1944-1946, 1949, 1950-1951, 1953-1958, 1960-1963 (Box 70)
  - Address Book, 1943-1944 (Box 70)
  - Statistical Pocket Book of Yugoslavia, 1958 (Box 70)
  - Preliminary Exam for Ph.D. Degree, 1924 (Box 71)
  - John R. Commons' Class[es] at Wisconsin (Box 71)
  - Coursework [?] (Box 71)
  - School Assignments, Institution Unknown (Box 71)
  - Classical Economists Class at Wisconsin (Box 71)
  - Papers for Classical Economists Class at Wisconsin (Box 71)
  - The High School Clipper, 1922 [Monmouth, Illinois] (Box 71)
  - Scrapbook [FRAGILE] (Box 71)
  - Bloc Notes [Memo Pads], circa late 1920s-early 1930s (Box 71)
  - Census Records, 1942 (Box 71)
  - Faith Hoover's Serenade (Box 71)
  - Faith Hoover's Sonata (Box 71)
  - Faith Hoover's Contemporary Germany, Austria, and Hungary, circa 1931, cover page-74 (Box 72)
  - Faith Hoover's Contemporary Germany, Austria, and Hungary, circa 1931, pages 75-146 (Box 72)
  - Faith Hoover's Contemporary Germany, Austria, and Hungary, circa 1931, pages 147-end page (Box 72)
  - Souvenirs (Box 72)
- Printed Material
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 72)
  - The Nation, 1928 Aug. 29, 1928 Sept. 12 (Box 72)
  - Royal Economic Society Reports, 1931-1932 (Box 72)
  - Monthly Review, 1932-1933 (Box 72)
  - National Recovery Administration, 1933 (Box 72)
  - Economic Conditions, Governmental Finance, United States Securities, 1932-1933 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous, 1920s (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous, 1930s (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Use and Misuse of Price History, 1944 (Box 74)
  - Draft Program of the League of Communists of Yugoslavia, 1958 (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 74)
  - New England Textiles and the New England Economy, 1956-1957 (Box 74)
  - New England Textiles and the New England Economy, 1958-1959 (Box 74)
  - Report of the New England Textile Industry, 1952 (Box 74)
  - The New England Economy, 1951 (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960s (Box 74)
  - Clippings, Miscellaneous and Hoover-Related (13 folders) (Box 75)
  - Economic Systems and Public Policy Essays in Honor of Calvin Bryce Hoover (Box 75)
  - Columbia University Honorary Degrees, 1902-1945 (Box 75)
  - Economic Life of Soviet Russia (Box 75)
  - Fellows of the Social Science Research Council, 1925-1951 (Box 75)
  - Proceedings of A Symposium on Economic Growth, sponsored by The American Bankers Association, 1963 (Box 76)
  - Russian Economic News, 1931-1933 (4 folders) (Box 76)
  - Economic Survey, State Bank of the U.S.S.R., 1928-1932 (Box 76)
  - Trade Union Bulletin, 1929 (Box 76)
  - State Bank of the U.S.S.R., 1921-1926 (Box 76)
  - State Bank of the U.S.S.R. Report, 1923-1924 (Box 76)
  - State Bank of the U.S.S.R., 1929-1930 (Box 76)
  - Revolutionary Age: An Organ of Marxism-Leninism in the United States, 1929-1930 (Box 76)
  - Thirteenth Annual Report of the Federal Reserve Board Covering Operations for the Year 1926 (Box 76)
  - Fourteenth Annual Report of the Federal Reserve Board Covering Operations for the Year 1927 (Box 76)
  - The Federal Antitrust Laws (Box 76)
  - Postwar Bilateral Payments Agreements (Box 76)
  - European Recovery Program (Box 76)
  - The I.W.W. in Theory and Practice (Box 76)
  - The Economy of Turkey (Box 76)
  - First Report to Congress of the Economic Cooperation Administration (Box 76)
  - The Yale Review, 1948 (Box 76)
  - Trade Union Organisation in U.S.S.R. (Box 76)
  - Facts and Figures regarding the U.S.S.R. (Box 76)
  - Protection of Labour in the U.S.S.R. (Box 76)
  - Social Insurance in the Soviet Union (Box 76)
  - Labor Under the Soviets (Box 76)
  - The New Agricultural Policy of Soviet Russia (Box 76)
  - The Sanctions of the Soviets (Box 76)
  - State Capitalism in Russia (Box 76)
  - A Survey of Unemployment Relief in Industry (Box 76)
  - U.S.S.R. Chamber of Commerce for Western Trade, Monthly Bulletin (Box 76)
  - The Trade Unions and Socialist Construction in U.S.S.R. (Box 76)
  - Cooperatives in Socialist Construction (Box 76)
  - Commerical Handbook of the U.S.S.R. for 1927 (Box 76)
  - Consumers' Cooperation in the Union of Socialist Soviet Republics (Box 76)
  - Foreign Language printed materials (Russian, German and French) (Box 77)
Related Material
Economics Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
The Economists' Papers Project.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Interview with Calvin B. Hoover, Sound Recording Collection, Oral History Project [Box R1].
University Archives, Duke University.
News Service Biographical Files: Hoover, Calvin B.
University Archives, Duke University.
Benjamin U. Ratchford Papers.
University Archives, Duke University.